<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>flask on Alfred Barrientos</title>
    <link>https://eacbarrientos.github.io/portfolio/tags/flask/</link>
    <description>Recent content in flask on Alfred Barrientos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eacbarrientos.github.io/portfolio/tags/flask/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: End-to-end Classification Model Project Solving Attrition Problem</title>
      <link>https://eacbarrientos.github.io/portfolio/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eacbarrientos.github.io/portfolio/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>The main objective is to solve this bank-related problem where a business manager of a consumer credit card portfolio is facing a severe customer attrition problem in the recent months. The business manager wants to leverage the power of data analytics to understand the primary reasons of attrition. She also wants to have an ability to understand the customers who are likely to close their accounts with the bank in the near future, so that she can focus her team&amp;rsquo;s efforts, well in advance to retain those customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Deploy ML Model using Flask and Pickle</title>
      <link>https://eacbarrientos.github.io/portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eacbarrientos.github.io/portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Considering that most Machine Learning models built don&amp;rsquo;t reach the deployment phase, I created this simple project to try deploying an ML Model using Flask and Pickle. This, perhaps, is a very simple project but I like how I was able to deploy a model which can be of use thru an html page using an API. Yay!
See the Full Project in Github Repository</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
